

■ Contact

Address: Izmir Town Canal Road Chung Lahore Pakistan. Whatsapp: +923013369414

Email: siddiqueitexpert@gmail.com Facebook: Muhammad Siddique



Highly recognized in the community, I can meet the challenges that your Institute will entrust me. I am a recognized expert in the field education & technologist.

■ Software

Windows 7, 8, Windows Server, Digital literacy and Web Development.

Informations

Languages: English, Urdu, Punjabi and slightly Arabic.

あ Hobbies

Technology and growth, Business, Community involvement, Sports, Biking, fishing, and Books Reading.

Muhammad Siddique

IT Expert

To work with a motivated and professional team and in a professional environment where I can gain practical experience, which would improve my technical, observational, decision making, and engineering and would strengthen my future career prospects.

An experienced teacher with a strong intrest in teaching that required both conceptual and analytical thinking .Want to get a position where I can utillize my skills and apply theoretically knowledge in order to get practical experience and play my role in the growth of organization.

Experience

School Teacher

2016-2019.

- Govt. High School Chung Lahore (1 year Internship)
- **♣** The Merit Education Complex Maraka Lahore.
- **♣** The Islamic Education Public School Chung Lahore.
 - ➤ Having Experience in Computer Science.
 - ➤ I can teach Computer Science at any level.
 - ➤ Having strong conceptual knowledge.

<u>Home Tutor</u> 2016-2019.

 Work with students to improve their reading, writing, and speaking skills.

Education

BSIT(Information Technology)

2016-2020.

- Information Technology.
- Govt College of Science Wahdat Roard Lahore.
- University Of The Punjab Lahore.

<u>F.Sc</u>

2013-2015.

- Pre-Engineering.
- CIMS College Lahore.
- Board of Intermidiate and Secondary Education Lahore.

Matriculation

2011-2013.

- Science Group.
- Govt High School Chung Lahore.
- Board of Intermidiate and Secondary Education Lahore.

Certificate

2017.

- MicroSoft.
- Government College Of Technology, Printing & Graphic Arts, Lahore.